tech-recipes.com 2011-01-19

# Privacy Information -- Everyday Ideas, QD Ideas

The administrators of this site are committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The information that is provided when a user registers, for example, will not be not be sold or used for unsolicited email. In the running of this web site, information is collected to make each userâ€™s experience more enjoyable. Anonymous information is obtained through this web structure. This type of information cannot be linked to a specific individual. For example, we will know how many people visit this page each day; however, we will not know the specific user name, email address, or any personal information about those visits. This anonymous information allows us to expand the popular aspects of this site and improve the less visited areas. If a user is not registered, only anonymous information is collected.

Personally identifiable information is data that uniquely refers to a specific user, such as a name or email address. This information is largely collected when a user registers. No personally identifiable information including email addresses or the data a user records into the â€œPersonal Informationâ€? or â€œProfile Informationâ€? sections will ever be sold or distributed. Information placed into these areas can be viewed by the public; the user may or may not choose to input data into this area. The user has the ability to hide his/her email address and online status from the public. Users often provide this information to help integrate themselves within the Tech-Recipes community.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when users visit our websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This information does not include information such as name, address, email address or telephone number. If you would like more information about this practice, please reference the privacy pages of those specific companies:

The functioning of this web site uses cookies for basic functions, such as the ability to recognize a logged-in user. Our third-party advertisers may place or identify unique cookies within your system. Our forums are publicly viewable. Any personal information placed in the forum may by viewed by anybody who visits our forums. Just as most people would not post information such as credit card numbers, addresses, phone numbers, or other such private information on a public bulletin board, users should limit the amount of personally identifiable information posted within the forums. The posting of personally identifiable information of other people is not allowed and will be removed.

The Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) requires that providers never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from people under the age of 13. If a user is found to be under the age of 13, we will not maintain that userâ€™s personally identifiable information. Additional information regarding protecting children’s privacy may be found at [http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.htm).

Please [contact us](http://www.tech-recipes.com/feedback) regarding questions about our privacy policy.
